Here it comes!
Ta-da!
Melon Cream Soda!
You can have it in Japan!
Nagoya Castle
It's up to the main gate of Nagoya Castle
We're walking!
It's kind of beautiful, isn't it?
Walking through a place that doesn't feel like Tokyo.
It's a little bit old, isn't it?
It's a little bit...
Yes, it's withered, and some of it has already fallen off.
It's like a good-bye ginkgo
Good-bye gingko
We both said "goodbye ginkgo", didn't we?
Here's a picture of that time
Already two years ago?
That was a long time ago.
Surprisingly, Misaki and I often go to places where we can get in touch with nature.
We've been to Sushi before.
It's like a really expensive place.
Like a restaurant.
Like a restaurant run by an old man.
It's impossible that we share a love of nature.
That's true.
But we also go to USJ together.
We're both very active.
We've been on bullet trips to Osaka.
Are you shaken? Yes, I'm shaking.
Misaki's hands are shaking.
I'll hold it.
I'm sorry.
It's just that my hands shake unconsciously.
But I like this time we have together.
I feel like we're friends now.
I usually think of you as a member.
Member
Workers
Workmates
It's like we don't really care about anything.
That's for sure.
We talk more in private, don't we?
Yes.
Of course we talk when we're working together, but...
But I feel like the temperature is different.
It's comfortable.
I'm going to wait for it.
There are a lot of people from overseas.
Is Nagoya town famous?
This is my first time in Nagoya.
I haven't had a chance to visit the castle
There's no reflection.
It's beautiful. I like the sound of the wind.
It's a little cloudy, but it's just the right amount of coolness.
Maybe it's my first time... to see Nagoya like this.
Didn't Rui tell you about this yesterday?
Rui didn't give it back to me today.
She didn't give it back to me today.
Really...
Rui?
Rui, right.
And Kira asked you to do it.
And she was like, "Sorry, sorry.
And like, sorry again.
I asked her to tell me, but she ignored me.
That's sad.
Isn't that what she said?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There he goes!
The front gate!
We've arrived at the front gate.
Enter.
Here come the members!
Here you go.
You can hear them in your ears during the concert.
Here come the members!
The moment you hear it...
We're already making eyes at each other.
We walk in together in the middle
The moment you nod
I'm fired up
I trust you.
It's not that much
The members appear
Okay, I'm off to buy tickets!
I'm here to buy tickets.
Here they are!
Ta-da!
It's big!
So big!
It's amazing!
I took a lot of pictures earlier.
I took so many pictures!
It was so good!
Killer Whale.
I'm here.
Oh, my God!
Look at this.
There's a tree.
Hey, I got a picture of this.
I got a picture of this.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's good.
That's great.
There you go.
Yes, sir.
Nagoya Castle is a lot of fun.
It's fun.
A little bit.
Various things...
I could see the shore
I could see it.
What do you want to do?
I see it.
Wow.
I'm so happy.
Hey...
I want to get a close-up of that orca, the golden orca.
Yeah, I want to get a solo shot of it.
Yeah.
Oh, that's nice.
We got to go around a lot.
We got around a lot.
It's delicious.
Yum! Yum!
First, the drinks came.
Cafe au lait.
It's a little bitter, don't you think?
Cheers.
Good morning.
Bon appétit.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
Yeah, I can't do it.
Latte and latté are different.
Of course they are.
I thought it was a latte.
Latte is espresso.
This is coffee.
Just right.
Delicious!
Nagoya has a great coffee culture.
Yeah.
And look at the manager!
And look at the manager! Elon cream soda!
The star of the show!
The sweetest!
You're the star of the show. Make sure you lift your body up.
Yes, sir.
We're here at EXP STUDIO Nagoya.
I changed.
I'm dressed now.
We're going to start the choreography lesson now.
I'll do my best.
TUYU
qualiyan
me
yeah
ana
I'll do it twice.
I'll do it a couple times.
One, two, three, four.
1,2,3,4
Perfect!
Okay, let's do the last one one more time, slowly.
How's everyone doing? Anything so far that you don't understand?
Do you think you'll be okay?
Want to try it a little faster?
Sure, let's do it a little faster.
That's a very fast song.
Let's do it a little faster.
Let's do the song this way.
Here we go!
Ready!
Three, two, one.
Next atra evidentialid comments
Do not do it!
If you are a straw man, you will recover EVERYTHING!
Next work will show how to do
Ja several earn side street